<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kohler Digital</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kohler Digital</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.137.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A RFM Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecommerce-rkc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ecommerce-rkc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- PROJECT SHIELDS --&gt;
&lt;!--
*** I&#39;m using markdown &#34;reference style&#34; links for readability.
*** Reference links are enclosed in brackets [ ] instead of parentheses ( ).
*** See the bottom of this document for the declaration of the reference variables
*** for contributors-url, forks-url, etc. This is an optional, concise syntax you may use.
*** https://www.markdownguide.org/basic-syntax/#reference-style-links
--&gt;
&lt;!-- ABOUT THE PROJECT --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was made for an essay of the University of Cumbria in the context of Msc in Data Analytics. It reviews the concepts of data science and analytics, then analyses an online luxury fashion C2C company&amp;rsquo;s dataset using Python, identifying weak correlations between social features/passRate and user sales.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gagnavist - A Datatþon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/datathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/datathon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gagnvist-datathon-2024---post-event-report&#34;&gt;GAGNVIST Datathon 2024 - Post-Event Report&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-event-designing-icelands-future-transit&#34;&gt;The Event: Designing Iceland&amp;rsquo;s Future Transit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organised by Hagstofa, The GAGNVIST Datathon 2024 brought together teams to tackle a fascinating challenge: optimising Borgarlínan&amp;rsquo;s route system in Iceland. Our team, Nerd Herd, approached this with a unique perspective - focusing on the human element of transit rather than just the technical infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal was to analysd and potentially redesign the proposed routes for Borgarlínan, using data from multiple sources including geographic data, population distribution from Hagstofan, employment centers, and existing Stræto bus routes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Potential Of Smart Tourism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/potential-smart-tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 13:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/potential-smart-tourism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Snjallferðaþjónusta nýtir nýjustu tækni eins og gervigreind og stórgögn til að skapa persónumiðaða og sjálfbæra ferðaupplifun. Þessi nálgun getur bætt upplifun ferðamanna, styrkt staðbundið viðskiptalíf og stuðlað að sjálfbærni í ferðaþjónustu, en krefst umtalsverðrar fjárfestingar í innviðum og þekkingu.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine this: A tourist arrives in Reykjavik, excited to explore Iceland. As they step off the plane, their smartphone lights up with a personalised welcome message and a curated list of attractions based on their interests. Throughout their stay, real-time data on weather conditions, Northern Lights visibility, and crowd levels at popular sites help them make the most of their visit. This isn’t science fiction - it’s the promise of smart tourism, and it’s closer than you might think.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samrt Tourism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/samrttourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 13:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/samrttourism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As an IT professional in Iceland’s tourism sector, I’ve witnessed firsthand the transformative power of data analytics. Our breathtaking landscapes and unique cultural experiences have drawn visitors from around the globe. But in today’s digital age, how can we leverage data to enhance these experiences and drive sustainable growth?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I dove deep into the world of data analytics in tourism, exploring its applications and potential impact on our industry. What I discovered was eye-opening. By harnessing the vast amounts of data generated by tourists - from social media posts to booking patterns - we can gain unprecedented insights into visitor preferences, behaviours, and pain points.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Smart Tourism Work in Iceland: From Vision to Reality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 13:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TLDR&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;em&gt;Iceland’s tourism industry is poised to embrace smart tourism, but faces unique challenges. Key recommendations include strengthening stakeholder collaboration, creating a centralized tourism data platform, and investing in widespread data literacy. The good news? Iceland’s compact size and tight-knit tourism community make rapid transformation possible.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-this-matters-now&#34;&gt;Why This Matters Now&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Iceland stands at a crossroads. As global tourism rebounds and evolves, destinations worldwide are racing to implement smart solutions. But Iceland’s unique context – its small market size, distinctive challenges, and opportunities – means it can’t simply copy-paste solutions from larger markets like Spain or Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transactional Analytics for a Spa</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rfm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rfm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- PROJECT SHIELDS --&gt;
&lt;!--
*** I&#39;m using markdown &#34;reference style&#34; links for readability.
*** Reference links are enclosed in brackets [ ] instead of parentheses ( ).
*** See the bottom of this document for the declaration of the reference variables
*** for contributors-url, forks-url, etc. This is an optional, concise syntax you may use.
*** https://www.markdownguide.org/basic-syntax/#reference-style-links
--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An exmple of report given to a spa. The goal was to analyse a sample of transactional data and derive actionable insight from the 4 months customer data. The code is accessible &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kohlerdigital/spa-analysis&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
